When your time is done in the army,
what do you want to be remembered for?
And it's the same thing I tell my
soldiers, when your name gets brought
up in conversation. I want it to at
least be something positive like oh
yeah, I worked with that guy like
we were stationed here, solid dude,
he's got your back and I know sometimes
our reputation can get ahead of us, so
make sure it's a good reputation. Make
sure that when you're brought up in
conversation it's for something
positive. So in terms of the lasting
impression that I want to leave behind
when I get out is that if my name is
ever brought up in conversation or they
see an old picture of me on a
wall at a company or a battalion
and be like, oh I remember that dude,
he was a solid guy. You know, maybe
he joked around a little too much, but
he got the job done to the best of his
ability.